sharesnack.com 2012-06-25

# SnackTools | Creative web applications

Thank you for visiting SnackTools.com (the "Web Site") and reviewing our Privacy Policy. Your privacy is important to us, and our policy is simple: we will collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Web Site unless you choose to provide that information. This Privacy Policy does not describe information collection practices on other sites, including those linked to or from the Web Site.

We do not collect nor distribute private data such as credit card numbers at all. Some personal information is recorded for SnackTools.com account purposes. All passwords are non-reversible encrypted (MD5) before being saved to the data base, to ensure that they (and your personal information) cannot be stolen from us, even in case of a hacking attack. We do not collect any passwords at all for users that are connecting using the Facebook Connect API as well as for those connecting with Twitter, Google and Yahoo APIs.

What Information Do We Gather?  
What Do We Do With the Information We Collect?  
Who Can Use the Information We Collect and How?  
How Do We Protect the Personal Information We Collect?  
How Do You Opt-out of Personal Information Sharing with Our Business Partners?  
How Do You Correct and Update Your Personal Information?  
What is Our Privacy Policy If You Are Under 13 Years of Age?  
What Happens When You Link to a Third-Party Web Site?  
What Happens When We Update Our Privacy Policy?  
What Happens If We Sell Our Business?  
What If You Have Questions?

### What Information Do We Gather?

When you visit our website ("Site"), we track information including the domain name and the name of the web page from which you entered our Site, and how much time you spend on each of our pages. We also collect information that is combined with other web visitors' information, such as how many times visitors click on each web page and the methods by which our Site was found. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you are using your browser on the Internet. We may collect IP addresses and website usage information from you when you visit our Site via the use of "cookies."

Cookies: A cookie is a small file that is stored on the hard drive of your computer ready for future access when you return to our Site. We use cookies to deliver web content specific to you and to keep track of your online order activity. Cookies cannot pass viruses, harm your computer or pass on private information such as an email address without the computer user's intervention. Cookies contain session identification numbers that allow our systems to recall previous sessions for authentication efforts and assemble information from our gathered data. You can configure your computer's browser to alert you when a site is attempting to send you a cookie and allow you to accept or refuse the cookie. In addition to cookies, we may use small bits of computer code called "one-pixel GIFs," "clear GIFs," or "web beacons" embedded in web pages to monitor website activity. We use this collected electronic data to better design our Site.

### What Do We Do With the Information We Collect?

You may be asked to provide personal information in certain fields on this Site. The personal information we collect is used only for the purpose we state at the time of collection.

This Site does not collect personally identifiable information when you browse the Site and request pages from our servers unless you voluntarily and knowingly provide such information to us. This means that we will not know your name, your email address, or any other personally identifiable information just because you browse the Site unless you:

  * access the Site from a link in an email that we have sent to you;
  * have created a profile and you either log-in to your account or choose to be remembered via your cookie, including on your web-enabled mobile device.

In these cases we will know who you are based on the information you previously supplied to us. When you request a page from our Site, our servers log the information provided in the HTTP request header including the IP number, the time of the request, the URL of your request and other information that is provided in the HTTP header. We collect the HTTP request header information in order to make our Site function correctly and provide you the functionality that you expect to see. We also use this information to personalize content presented to you, better understand how visitors use our Site and how we can better tune it, its contents, and functionality to meet your needs.

You can delete cookies from your hard drive at any time. You can set your Internet browser so that it will not allow cookies to be stored on your device. This may reduce functionality of SnackTools.com and may mean that certain features or content will not be available to you. Further information on how to prevent cookies from being stored on your device can be found on [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) under the 'manage cookies' section. Alternatively, you can access further information by going to the help menu within your Internet browser. To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

### Who Can Use the Information We Collect and How?

We may provide your information to third parties, or third parties may collect information from you on our behalf if we have contracted with that third party to provide some part of the information or service that you have requested. By written agreement, these third parties are required to implement similar security measures and will process your information only as authorized by us to fulfill the service that they have been contracted to provide.

Other than those who act on our behalf and except as explained in this Policy, information you provide at this Site will not be transferred to unrelated third parties, unless we have your permission to do so. However, please note that personal information provided to this Site is subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants or orders.

We allow you to control the disclosure of your non-public personal information to third parties for the marketing of third-party products and services (i.e., your consent is required for disclosure). We must disclose information, when requested, to comply with court orders or subpoenas.

### How Do We Protect the Personal Information We Collect?

Your privacy and the security of your personal information are important to us. We maintain and protect the security of our servers and your personal information. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, however. Accordingly, despite the safeguards in place to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, or to or from our online products or services. You transmit all such information at your own risk. However, once we receive your personal information, we will undertake all commercially reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. To secure the information we collect online, prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure only appropriate use of information, we have established appropriate physical, electronic and management safeguards. We require user names and passwords to access sensitive data. Unless you authorize unencrypted transmission, we will use industry standard encryption methods to protect your data transmission.

### How Do You Opt-out of Personal Information Sharing with Our Business Partners?

Other than agents who act on our behalf, the information you provide through our Site will not be transferred to unrelated third parties unless we have your permission to do so. You can also opt out of our marketing emails at any time by contacting us at [contact@snacktools.com](mailto:contact@snacktools.com) (with subject "OPT OUT") or by sending us a post card to "OPT OUT" Smartketer LLC, 200 East Big Beaver Road, Troy, Mi. 48083 - USA.

### How Do You Correct and Update Your Personal Information?

You can change or correct your account information at any time by logging into your SnackTools account.

### What is Our Privacy Policy If You Are Under 13 Years of Age?

The Web Site is not directed to children under thirteen (13) years of age, and children under such age must not use the web site or services offered on it to submit any individually identifiable information about themselves.

### What Happens When You Link to a Third-Party Web Site?

If you click on a link and go to another site, you will be subject to that website’s privacy policy. If we conduct business with that website such that we need to exchange personally identifiable information, we will make sure that the business has a privacy policy just as protective as ours. We encourage you to read the posted privacy policy statement at any website before submitting any personal information at all.

### What About Intellectual Property? Copyrights? Trademarks?

**_Copyrights_**

The materials found on the Web Site are protected by United States and other copyright laws, except for works of the United States Government pursuant to 1 U.S.C. Section 105. The selection, arrangement and presentation of all materials (including information in the public domain), and the overall design of the Web Site are copyright © 2007, Smartketer LLC. Permission is granted to view and print materials from SnackTools.com for the non-commercial purpose of viewing, reading and retaining for reference. Any other copying, distribution, retransmission or modification of information or materials on this site, whether in electronic or hard copy form, without the express prior written permission of Smartketer LLC, is strictly prohibited.

**_Trademarks_**

SnackTools.com, BannerSnack.com, PhotoSnack.com, Podsnack.com, TubeSnack.com, QuizSnack.com, FlipSnack.com, SlideSnack.com, FileSnack.com, ShareSnack.com, SanckWebsites.com and Smartketer are trademarks and service marks of Smartketer LLC. For more information, please see the Terms of Service.

### What Happens When We Update Our Privacy Policy?

We may on occasion update our Policy. Your acceptance of any minor changes to this Policy is indicated by your continued use of our Services. If we make any material changes to our Policy, we will post a notice about the change at a prominent location on our Site. We encourage you to periodically review our Site and this Policy for any changes.

### What Happens If We Sell Our Business?

While we do not anticipate it, every business nowadays should plan for the possibility that it might sell certain or all of its assets to another company or individual, or that it might buy certain assets of another company or individual. If all or part of the company is sold, merged or otherwise transferred to another entity, the personal information you have provided to us may be transferred as part of that transaction. However, we will take steps to ensure that your personal information is used in a manner consistent with the provisions of our Policy.

### What If You Have Questions?

Questions or comments regarding the Web Site should be sent by e-mail to SnackTools.com support or by U.S. mail to Smartketer LLC, 200 East Big Beaver Road, Troy, Mi. 48083 - USA.
